Mom, Dad
Cynthia
Let's go
Let's go inside and take a look
This house is really impressive
Must have cost a fortune
Two stories
A million at least
Plus the renovations
Two million at the minimum
The Liu family is truly blessed
In the past, the Liu family
had the worst house in the village
It was almost collapsing
Now no one can match their success
You really need to raise a good son
Or you won't have a home when you are old
Daniel lost everything again this time
And he owes a lot to loan sharks
Heard he can't pay them back
His house and land were seized
My house
If you can't pay your debts
This house is mine now
Get out
Lewes
I am so miserable
Why is your life getting better and better
I'm talking to you
You are still one million short
You have three days
Or I will break your legs
Get out
I won't just accept my fate
Lewes, just you wait